export const categories = [
    { id: 0, name: 'Geography' },
    { id: 1, name: 'History' },
    { id: 2, name: 'Literature' },
    { id: 3, name: 'Science' },
];

export const questions = [
    { id: 0, category_id: 0, question: "What is de capital of Argentina?", answer: "Buenos Aires", options: ["Buenos Aires", "Cordoba", "Rosario", "La Plata"] },
    { id: 1, category_id: 0, question: "What is de capital of Brazil?", answer: "Brasilia", options: ["Brasilia", "Rio de Janeiro", "Sao Paulo", "Salvador"] },
    { id: 2, category_id: 0, question: "What is de capital of Chile?", answer: "Santiago", options: ["Santiago", "Valdivia", "Concepcion", "Puerto Montt"] },
    { id: 3, category_id: 0, question: "What is de capital of Colombia?", answer: "Bogota", options: ["Bogota", "Cali", "Medellin", "Barranquilla"] },
    { id: 4, category_id: 0, question: "What is de capital of Ecuador?", answer: "Quito", options: ["Quito", "Guayaquil", "Ambato", "Tallinn"] },

    { id: 11, category_id: 1, question: "When was the first World War?", answer: "1914-1918", options: ["1914-1918", "1939-1945", "1939-1945", "1914-1918"] },
    { id: 12, category_id: 1, question: "When was the second World War?", answer: "1939-1945", options: ["1914-1918", "1939-1945", "1939-1945", "1914-1918"] },

    { id: 13, category_id: 2, question: "Who is the author of the book 'The Lord of the Rings'?", answer: "J.R.R. Tolkien", options: ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "J.D. Salinger", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"] },
    { id: 14, category_id: 2, question: "Who is the author of the book 'The Hobbit'?", answer: "J.R.R. Tolkien", options: ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "J.D. Salinger", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"] },
    { id: 15, category_id: 2, question: "Who is the author of the book 'The Catcher in the Rye'?", answer: "J.D. Salinger", options: ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "J.D. Salinger", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"] },
    { id: 16, category_id: 2, question: "Who is the author of the book 'The Great Gatsby'?", answer: "F. Scott Fitzgerald", options: ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "J.D. Salinger", "F. Scott Fitzgerald"] },

    { id: 17, category_id: 3, question: "What is chemical symbol for 'Carbon'?", answer: "Carbon", options: ["Carbon", "c", "a", "sss"] },
    { id: 18, category_id: 3, question: "What is chemical symbol for 'Hydrogen'?", answer: "Hydrogen", options: ["Hydrogen", "sd", "sd", "aaaaa"] },
    { id: 19, category_id: 3, question: "What is chemical symbol for 'Oxygen'?", answer: "Oxygen", options: ["Oxygen", "sda", "aasd", "aaaaaa"] },
    { id: 20, category_id: 3, question: "What is chemical symbol for 'Nitrogen'?", answer: "Nitrogen", options: ["Nitrogen", "aaaaa", "sdasd", "aaaaa"] },

]; 